<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</origin><pubdate>20180619</pubdate><title>Wildlife Management Unit</title><geoform>vector digital data</geoform><pubinfo><pubplace>Edmonton, Alberta</pubplace><publish>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</publish></pubinfo><ftname Sync="TRUE">BASEFEAT.BF_GEO_WLDLFE_MGMT_UNT_POLYGON</ftname><onlink>https://maps.alberta.ca/genesis/rest/services/Fish_and_Wildlife_Administrative_Area/Latest/MapServer</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>The Wildlife Management Unit (WMU) dataset is comprised of all the polygons that represent the Wildlife Management Units in Alberta.  WMU is an area of wildlife managed under Wildlife Act, Alberta Regulation 143/79.</abstract><purpose>The Wildlife Management Unit dataset provides users with GIS ready polygonal representation of all the Wildlife Management Units in the province of Alberta, and is suitable for indexing or analysis purposes.
			</purpose><supplinf>Defining document is Wildlife Act AR 143/97, Schedule 9. </supplinf><langdata>en</langdata></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>20180616</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo><current>ground condition</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>As needed</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>
-121.000000</westbc><eastbc>
-109.000000</eastbc><northbc>
61.000000</northbc><southbc>
48.000000</southbc></bounding><lboundng><leftbc Sync="TRUE">-121.000000</leftbc><rightbc Sync="TRUE">-109.000000</rightbc><bottombc Sync="TRUE">48.000000</bottombc><topbc Sync="TRUE">61.000000</topbc></lboundng></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>boundaries</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>none</themekt><themekey>Wildlife Management Unit</themekey><themekey>Wildlife Management Units</themekey><themekey>wmu</themekey></theme></keywords><accconst>To access the data you must agree to the terms of the Open Government Licence - Alberta</accconst><useconst>Your use of the information will be governed by the terms of the Open Government Licence - Alberta, in force as of the date you accessed the information.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>14th Floor, Oxbridge Place</address><address>9820 - 106 Street NW</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>Alberta</state><postal>T5K 2J6</postal><country>Canada</country></cntaddr><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><hours>08:15 to 16:30 Monday to Friday</hours><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntfax>7804220712</cntfax><cntinst>This is the point of contact regarding the creation of, and characteristics of, the data set. Queries about the creation and/or characteristics of the data set submitted through facsimile or electronic mail must include the salutation "Attention: Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division; Dataset: Wildlife Management Unit". For Distribution Information contact instructions, refer to the Distribution Information section of this metadata record. For Metadata Information contact instructions, refer to the Metadata Reference Information section of this metadata record.</cntinst></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</datacred><secinfo><secsys>Government of Alberta Data and Information Security Classification</secsys><secclass>Public</secclass></secinfo><native>Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 2; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.2.4.1420</native><natvform>SDE Feature Class</natvform></idinfo><dataqual><lineage><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><pubinfo><pubplace>Edmonton, Alberta</pubplace><publish>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</publish></pubinfo><title>Base Features Source Data includes arc layers of ATS, Hydrography, Hypsography, Access and Master Height of Land </title><origin>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</origin></citeinfo></srccite></srcinfo><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><title>Alberta Data Partnerships Cadastral Source Data includes block, lot, plan, ownership, right-of-way and legal subdivision arcs </title><origin>Alberta Data Partnerships Ltd. </origin><pubinfo><pubplace>Calgary, Alberta </pubplace><publish>Alberta Data Partnerships </publish></pubinfo></citeinfo></srccite></srcinfo><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><title>Other sources include digital reference file and constructed arcs </title><origin>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</origin><pubinfo><pubplace>Edmonton, Alberta </pubplace><publish>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</publish></pubinfo></citeinfo></srccite></srcinfo><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><title>Base Features Geoadministrative Areas Provincial Boundary and National Park </title><origin>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</origin><pubinfo><pubplace>Edmonton, Alberta </pubplace><publish>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</publish></pubinfo></citeinfo></srccite></srcinfo><procstep><procdesc>Initial compilation. The Regulation is not well defined and clear. There are a number of unnamed creeks, streams, roads, locally known roads, etc. described. Boundaries compiled under these conditions were according to the best interpretation knowledge of the compiler. There is an issue of correctness of the GA coverage due to the insufficient information provided by Data Authority, based on the above conditions. Part 2 of the Regulation which mainly describes the Provincial Park and other associated GA Wildlife Management Units have not been compiled as those associated GA coverages were not available at that time.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>200101</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>The Wildlife Management Unit boundary is built by selecting and putting available Source Data (described below) into an edit environment of the layer, to assemble the Geoadministrative Areas (GA) boundary. The GA boundary built uses Base Features (BF) Source Data which includes arc layers of Alberta Township System (ATS), Hydrography, Hypsography and Access. In cases where BF Source Data does not exist, Alberta Data Partnerships (ADP) Cadastral Source Data including block, lot, plan, ownership and right-of-way are used.  Legal Subdivision (LSD) arcs supplied by ADP are also used. 
ATS data layer is considered to be the foundation by which all other Source Data should be registered with when the GA boundary layer is compiled.  The Cadastral Source Data maintained by ADP is used in the hierarchy order of block, lot, plan and right-of-way; regardless which version it is. The ADP cadastral representation of ATS and Hydrography is not used.  The ADP LSD arcs are used for boundary segments that are interpreted as aligning with legal subdivision lines according to the defining document; but the representation of Section, Quarter Section and Road Allowance are not allowed to be used as these lines should be derived from the BF ATS Source Data. 
If none of the above Source Data is available and the defining document refers a specific elevation or contour, Hypsography contour data is used.  If no source arc for the particular contour or elevation exists, interpolation of the contours or elevation graphically is obtained by averaging between successive contours on either side of the range of elevation values.  If the defining document describes a mountain peak, interpretation of the contours to determine the highest point of the peak is determined or in certain cases a spot height point in the Hypsography cartographic layer is used to identify the peak.  If the defining document describes a boundary segment as Height-of-Land (HOL), HOL data is captured by digitization or graphical construction.
In cases if the GA boundary is described, but no Source Data is available except from a digital reference file provided by data authority, with data authority's expressed permission, arcs are copied from the digital reference file.
Segments of the boundary which adjoin to Provincial Boundary or National Park, arcs are copied from these 2 layers to define the GA boundary so that the layer does conform to these 2 key layers.
Once all the Source Data has been copied and put into the edit environment, Constructed arcs are used to close polygon in cases where a gap between 2 Source Data arcs exceeds 0.001 meters.  If a gap is less than 0.001 meters, one of the Source Data is extended to close the polygon, in accordance with the Source Data edit hierarchy i.e. with the highest order of importance to the least importance which is in the order of ATS, Hydrography, Hypsography, ADP data, Access, Height-of-Land or digitized arcs and digital reference file.  
Spatial relationship of the boundary layer compiled is maintained with the Base Features (BF) Source data and other Source Data with the geometry of all the Source Data remains unaltered throughout the editing process.  Edit tolerance is set to zero for node snap and arc snap.  The GA polygons compiled have all the linework precisely closed.
Attribute tables are created according to item definition, with only one label point exists per GA polygon.  
Clean processes on the Source Data beyond the tolerances specified above are prohibited. Source Data is edited manually in order to maintain polygon topology using BUILD processes.  After polygons are built, they are attributed according to the Base Features GA Specification table standard i.e. CODE and NAME. The formatted polygon attribute values are validated with Wildlife Management Unit codes and legal names obtained from the Department.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>20020326</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Revised data structure. The Regulation has been revised by Fish and Wildlife, in cases, due to description discrepancies. Contact data authority for the revised set of Regulation. Part 2 Regulation: Provincial Park Wildlife Management Unit (600) was not captured, as directed by data authority. Specific Provincial Park, Provincial Recreation Area and DND Military Base WMUs include exclusions captured by those specific reference GA layers. Exterior road allowances that are not part of the specific reference GA layers are included in the WMU layer according to the appropriate quarter-section of ATS fabric i.e. quarter-sections lying to the east of road allowances. These specific WMU boundaries were also adjusted to meet the adjoining regular Part 1Regulation WMU boundaries, as agreed upon by Parks and Protected Areas.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>200509</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>WMU 542 is split into 541 and 542</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>200704</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>WMU 503, 512, 515 boundaries reversed back to the initial Regulation legal descriptions. Spelling corrections of `North Porcupine Hill' (Code 00304) and `South Porcupine Hill' (Code 00305) to 'North Porcupine Hills' and 'South Porcupine Hills'.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>200706</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Reconciled to ATS v4.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>200802</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Boundary correction between #303 &amp; #306.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>201007</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Reconciled and conformed to ATS V4.1 Alberta Provincial Boundary which was compiled by Alberta Data Partnerships Ltd. (ADP) on behalf of the Government of Alberta (GOA).  The ATS V4.1 Alberta Provincial Boundary is considered definitive for GOA use which supersedes all previous versions.  The  ATS V4.1 Alberta Provincial Boundary was compiled in 8th decimal place geographic coordinates (GCS_North_American_1983) and which was geoprocessed to NAD 1983 10 TM AEP Forest coordinate system, using ESRI ArcGIS application.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>201109</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>AR 143/97 (consolidated up to 200/2011) Schedule 9
a. Lakeland Provincial Park WMU #651 &amp; Lac La Biche WMU #503, Lakeland  
    Provincial Recreation Area WMU #841
    Boundary correction: Adjustment of inclusion/exclusion of road allowances 
    made between Provincial Park &amp; Provincial Recreation Area impacts WMU 
    #651, #503 &amp; #841.
b. Writing-on-Stone Provincial Park WMU #18 &amp; Aden WMU #104 
    Update: Revised O.C. of Writing-on-Stone Provincial Park (O.C. 408/2011 
    Sept. 9, 2011) of boundary adjustment and to include newly acquired lands.  
    This impacts WMU #718 &amp; #104.
c. Air Weapons Ranges WMU #726 &amp; Heart Lake WMU #515, Winefred Lake 
    WMU #517
    Update: An update on DND Air Weapons Range was made in June 2011, 
    based on an Amended Agreement made between the Canada/Alberta Cold 
    Lake Air Weapons Range, well back in June 30 1995.  The amended 
    boundary on DND Air Weapons Range impacts WMU #726, #515 &amp; #517.
d. West Wainwright WMU #728 &amp; Hardisty WMU #232 
    Correction: A portion of the Canadian Forces Base Wainwright (DND Military 
    Base) sitting to the NW of the main base had been missing and was added in. 
    This impacts WMU #728 &amp; #232.
e. Evans-Thomas Recreation Area WMU #794 &amp; Kananaskis River WMU #408
    Correction: Boundary correction of Evans-Thomas Provincial Recreation Area, 
    along Highway 40 in 23-9-5 impacts WMU #794 &amp; #408.
f.  Lakeland Provincial Recreation Area WMU #841 &amp; Heart Lake WMU #515
    Correction: Adjustment of inclusion/exclusion of road allowances along the 
    peripheral of Lakeland Provincial Recreation Area impacts WMU #841 &amp; #515.
g. Cooking Lake - Blackfoot Grazing, Wildlife and Recreation Area WMU #936 &amp; 
    Edmonton WMU #248, Beaver Hill WMU #242
    Correction: Adjustment of inclusion/exclusion of road allowances along the W 
    side of Cooking Lake - Blackfoot Grazing, Wildlife Provincial Recreation Area 
    impacts WMU #936, #248 &amp; #242</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>201202</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>AR 143/97 (consolidated up to 2012.04.10) Schedule 9: O'Chiese WMU #330 and Alder Flats WMU #332 - Regulation amendment. Boundary change.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>201204</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Correction: Two Blueberry WMU #359 exist.  One is corrected to Saddle Hills WMU #358.</procdesc><proccont><cntinfo><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp></cntinfo></proccont><procdate>201205</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>a. WMU 248 Edmonton - Boundary change. Amend Regulation AR 143/97, Schedule 9, Part 1 #55
b. WMU 250 Red Water - Boundary change. Amend Regulation AR 143/97, Schedule 9, Part 1 #56
c. WMU 523 Kimiwan-Winagami Lakes - Amalgamate land transfer from WMU 926 Greene Valley.  Amend Regulation AR 143/97, Schedule 9, Part 1 #154
d. WMU 926 Greene Valley - Unit dissolve.  Land transfers to WMU 523 Kimiwan-Winagami Lakes.  Amend Regulation AR 143/97, Schedule 9, Part 2 #15
e. Update western boundary of 'WMU 439 Solomon', initiated by the National Park boundary adjustment in vicinity from Ogre Canyon to Boule Roche i.e. in the area of Sec 7-50-27-w5 to Sec 13-50-28-w5</procdesc><procdate>201805</procdate></procstep></lineage><logic>Boundary that falls along river or water body refers to Bed and Shore which can be perennial or intermittent / recurring.</logic></dataqual><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf><esriterm Name="ab_base.DBO.WMU_2018"><efeatyp Sync="TRUE">Simple</efeatyp><efeageom code="4" Sync="TRUE"/><esritopo Sync="TRUE">FALSE</esritopo><efeacnt Sync="TRUE">0</efeacnt><spindex Sync="TRUE">TRUE</spindex><linrefer Sync="TRUE">FALSE</linrefer></esriterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><geodetic><horizdn>North American Datum of 1983</horizdn><ellips>Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257222</denflat></geodetic><cordsysn><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn></cordsysn></horizsys><vertdef><altsys><altres>1.000000</altres><altenc>Explicit elevation coordinate included with horizontal coordinates</altenc></altsys></vertdef></spref><eainfo><detailed Name="ab_base.DBO.WMU_2018"><enttyp><enttypl>BaseFeatures.GDB.BF_GEO_WLDLFE_MGMT_UNT_POLYGON</enttypl><enttypd>Wildlife Act AR 143/97, Schedule 9</enttypd><enttypds>Statutes of Alberta</enttypds><enttypt Sync="TRUE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">0</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>SHAPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Geometry</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">WMUNIT_NAM</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">WMUNIT_NAM</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">80</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">WMUNIT_COD</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">WMUNIT_COD</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">5</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">OBJECTID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">OID</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Shape.STArea()</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape.STArea()</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">0</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Shape.STLength()</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape.STLength()</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">0</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>AltaLIS Ltd.</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>2540 - 5th Avenue NW</address><city>Calgary</city><state>Alberta</state><postal>T2N 0T5</postal><country>Canada</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>4037163490</cntvoice><cntfax>4037163494</cntfax><cntemail>info@altalis.com</cntemail><hours>08:00 to 16:30 Monday to Friday</hours><cntinst>The layer is a part of the Base Features product which can be accessed and downloaded via the Open Data option from AltaLIS: http://www.altalis.com/products/base/20k_base_features.html </cntinst></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>Live Data and Maps</resdesc><distliab>Under the terms of the Open Government Licence - Alberta, the Information is licensed as is, and the Information Provider excludes all representations, warranties, obligations, and liabilities, whether express or implied, to the maximum extent permitted by law. The Information Provider is not liable for any errors or omissions in the Information, and will not under any circumstances be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential, or other loss, injury or damage caused by its use or otherwise arising in connection with this licence or the Information, even if specifically advised of the possibility of such loss, injury or damage.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI Shapefile </formname><filedec>File compression technology shall be utilized when required. AltaLIS presently utilizes WinZip. </filedec></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>http://www.altalis.com/products/base/20k_base_features.html</networkr></networka></computer><accinstr>The layer is a part of the Base Features product which can be accessed and downloaded via the Open Data option from AltaLIS: http://www.altalis.com/products/base/20k_base_features.html</accinstr></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>This layer is included in the Base Features product for free under the Open Government Licence - Alberta. </fees><ordering>The layer is a part of the Base Features product which can be accessed and downloaded via the Open Data option from AltaLIS: http://www.altalis.com/products/base/20k_base_features.html</ordering><turnarnd>Direct download</turnarnd></stdorder><custom>For a fee, custom cuts to the layer can be made as part of the Base Features bundle by contacting an AltaLIS representative at 403-716-3490 or by email at info@altalis.com.</custom><techpreq>To utilize digital information, specialized software may be required. Digital information required specialized graphics or GIS software (i.e. ArcInfo, ArcView, ArcGIS, or MicroStation).</techpreq><availabl><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>Monday to Sunday</caldate><time>24 hours</time></sngdate></timeinfo></availabl></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20180619</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>Alberta Environment and Parks, Government of Alberta</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>14th Floor, Oxbridge Place</address><address>9820 - 106 Street NW</address><city>Edmonton</city><state>Alberta</state><postal>T5K 2J6</postal><country>Canada</country></cntaddr><cntemail>AEP.GDAMetadata@gov.ab.ca</cntemail><hours>08:15 to 16:30 Monday to Friday</hours><cntpos>Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division</cntpos><cntfax>7804220712</cntfax><cntinst>This is the point of contact regarding the creation of, and characteristics of, metadata for the data set. Queries about the creation and/or characteristics of the metadata submitted through facsimile or electronic mail must include the salutation "Attention: Information and Data Provisioning Services, Informatics Branch, Corporate Services Division; Dataset: Wildlife Management Unit". For Distribution Information contact instructions, refer to the Distribution Information section of this metadata record.</cntinst></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc><langmeta Sync="TRUE">en</langmeta></metainfo><Esri><ModDate>20180703</ModDate><ModTime>13142900</ModTime><CreaDate>20190225</CreaDate><CreaTime>15030100</CreaTime><SyncOnce>FALSE</SyncOnce><SyncDate>20180703</SyncDate><SyncTime>13142900</SyncTime><DataProperties><lineage><Process Date="20100727" Time="112537" ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\DeleteFeatures">DeleteFeatures "Database Connections\BASEFEAT@GEO1.CNS5.ENV.GOV.AB.CA.sde\BASEFEAT.BF_GEO_WLDLFE_MGMT_UNT_POLYGON" "Database Connections\BASEFEAT@GEO1.CNS5.ENV.GOV.AB.CA.sde\BASEFEAT.BF_GEO_WLDLFE_MGMT_UNT_POLYGON"</Process><Process ToolSource="c:\program files (x86)\arcgis\desktop10.2\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Conversion Tools.tbx\FeatureClassToFeatureClass" Date="20180703" Time="131436">FeatureClassToFeatureClass "E:\GIS\GeoAdmin\Altalis\03JULY2018\Wildlife Management Unit.shp" "Database Connections\ab_base.sde\ab_base.DBO.GeoAdmin" WMU_2018 # "WMUNIT_NAM "WMUNIT_NAM" true true false 80 Text 0 0 ,First,#,E:\GIS\GeoAdmin\Altalis\03JULY2018\Wildlife Management Unit.shp,WMUNIT_NAM,-1,-1;WMUNIT_COD "WMUNIT_COD" true true false 5 Text 0 0 ,First,#,E:\GIS\GeoAdmin\Altalis\03JULY2018\Wildlife Management Unit.shp,WMUNIT_COD,-1,-1" #</Process></lineage><itemProps><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">Server=GEOSPATIALSDE; Service=sde:sqlserver:GEOSPATIALSDE\ABMISDE; Database=ab_base; User=sa; Version=dbo.DEFAULT</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">ArcSDE Connection</protocol></itemLocation><itemName Sync="TRUE">ab_base.DBO.WMU_2018</itemName><imsContentType Sync="TRUE">002</imsContentType></itemProps><coordRef><type Sync="TRUE">Projected</type><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn><csUnits Sync="TRUE">Linear Unit: Meter (1.000000)</csUnits><projcsn Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_10TM_AEP_Forest</projcsn><peXml Sync="TRUE">&lt;ProjectedCoordinateSystem xsi:type='typens:ProjectedCoordinateSystem' xmlns:xsi='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance' xmlns:xs='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema' xmlns:typens='http://www.esri.com/schemas/ArcGIS/10.1'&gt;&lt;WKT&gt;PROJCS[&amp;quot;NAD_1983_10TM_AEP_Forest&amp;quot;,GEOGCS[&amp;quot;GCS_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,DATUM[&amp;quot;D_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,SPHEROID[&amp;quot;GRS_1980&amp;quot;,6378137.0,298.257222101]],PRIMEM[&amp;quot;Greenwich&amp;quot;,0.0],UNIT[&amp;quot;Degree&amp;quot;,0.0174532925199433]],PROJECTION[&amp;quot;Transverse_Mercator&amp;quot;],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Easting&amp;quot;,500000.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Northing&amp;quot;,0.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Central_Meridian&amp;quot;,-115.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Scale_Factor&amp;quot;,0.9992],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Latitude_Of_Origin&amp;quot;,0.0],UNIT[&amp;quot;Meter&amp;quot;,1.0],AUTHORITY[&amp;quot;EPSG&amp;quot;,3400]]&lt;/WKT&gt;&lt;XOrigin&gt;-5118700&lt;/XOrigin&gt;&lt;YOrigin&gt;-9994100&lt;/YOrigin&gt;&lt;XYScale&gt;10000&lt;/XYScale&gt;&lt;ZOrigin&gt;0&lt;/ZOrigin&gt;&lt;ZScale&gt;1&lt;/ZScale&gt;&lt;MOrigin&gt;0&lt;/MOrigin&gt;&lt;MScale&gt;1&lt;/MScale&gt;&lt;XYTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/XYTolerance&gt;&lt;ZTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/ZTolerance&gt;&lt;MTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/MTolerance&gt;&lt;HighPrecision&gt;true&lt;/HighPrecision&gt;&lt;WKID&gt;102184&lt;/WKID&gt;&lt;LatestWKID&gt;3400&lt;/LatestWKID&gt;&lt;/ProjectedCoordinateSystem&gt;</peXml></coordRef></DataProperties><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><ArcGISstyle>FGDC CSDGM Metadata</ArcGISstyle></Esri><distInfo><distributor><distorTran><onLineSrc><orDesc Sync="TRUE">002</orDesc></onLineSrc></distorTran></distributor><distFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">SDE Feature Class</formatName></distFormat></distInfo><dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE"> Version 6.2 (Build 9200) ; Esri ArcGIS 10.2.2.3552</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="TRUE">ab_base.DBO.WMU_2018</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd value="005" Sync="TRUE"/></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd value="001" Sync="TRUE"/></spatRpType></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></mdLang><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005" Sync="TRUE"/></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode code="3400" Sync="TRUE"/><idCodeSpace Sync="TRUE">EPSG</idCodeSpace><idVersion Sync="TRUE">8.2.6</idVersion></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><geometObjs Name="ab_base.DBO.WMU_2018"><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd value="002" Sync="TRUE"/></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt Sync="TRUE">0</geoObjCnt></geometObjs><topLvl><TopoLevCd value="001" Sync="TRUE"/></topLvl></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20180703</mdDateSt></metadata>
